<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>techbytes on FinOps Solutions</title>
    <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/tags/techbytes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in techbytes on FinOps Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://m2mconect.github.io/tags/techbytes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Disassemble the problem</title>
      <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/07/disassemble_the_problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/07/disassemble_the_problem/</guid>
      <description>Our next step as a Data Analyst is to divide the problem into smaller, manageable, solvable chunks (disassemble).
Often, your problem will be vague, like this: &amp;ldquo;How do we increase Sales?&amp;rdquo;. The best approach to answer those big problems is to answer the smaller problems, which you’ve analyzed out of the big problem. For instance
How do we increase sales? could be split into
What do our best customers want from us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining the Problem</title>
      <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/06/defining_the_problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/06/defining_the_problem/</guid>
      <description>Doing data analysis without explicitly defining your problem or goal is like heading out on a road trip without having decided on a destination.
If you are an analyst and need an hour long slide show to make your point, then often most likely you haven&amp;rsquo;t focused enough on your problem and are throwing your client (boss) with a sea of information as a way of ducking your obligation to solve a problem and recommend a decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analyst</title>
      <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/05/data_analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2021/01/05/data_analyst/</guid>
      <description>So let&amp;rsquo;s say there is a business run by someone for the past 3+ years selling few products primarily targeted for teens. Business has been consistently growing and the team is also expanding. So the CEO hires you (a data analyst) with the hope that you can provide valuable analysis which will help her figure out how to increase sales.
People who possess Data Analysis skills have a massive edge on everyone else, because they understand what to do with all the humongous data, a business has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Technology</title>
      <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2019/02/23/impact_of_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2019/02/23/impact_of_technology/</guid>
      <description>All revolutions are, until they happen, then they are historical inevitabilities - David Mitchell, Cloud Atlas
Today’s world is an image of a revolution that has happened. We have gone through numerous revolutions to come to this stage. Though there are a number of revolutions around us throughout the various centuries, all these can be classified into three or in other words they can all be boxed into one of the following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fintech</title>
      <link>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2019/01/10/fintech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://m2mconect.github.io/blog/2019/01/10/fintech/</guid>
      <description>There has been a new jargon in financial industry &amp;ldquo;Fintech&amp;rdquo; which has been floating around for the past few years. &amp;ldquo;Fintech&amp;rdquo; are technology-first (software based) companies that leverage software to compete with traditional financial institutions.
Traditional brick and mortar financial institutions have to somehow pass their physical location operational costs to their customers in one way or other. Online-only financial institutions fully pass these savings to their customers.
There are already many online-only financial institutions which have made their mark.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
